module.exports = [
    {
      "category": "MLB 101",
      "questions": [
        {
          "points": 100,
          "question": "How many Strikes result in a batter getting strukeout", 
          "answer": "3"
        },
        {
          "points": 200,
          "question": "What Does DH stand for in a lineup card",
          "answer": "Designated Hitter"
        },
        {
          "points": 300,
          "question": "How Many Innings in a reglation MLB Game",
          "answer": "9"
        },
        {
          "points": 400,
          "question": "Football and Basketball have Referees, Baseball has",
          "answer": "Umpires"
        },
        {
            "points": 500,
            "question": "Hall of Famer who broke the color barrier in 1947",
            "answer": "Jackie Robinson"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "NBA Fun",
      "questions": [
        {
          "points": 100,
          "question": "How Many Teams are in the NBA",
          "answer": "30"
        },
        {
          "points": 200,
          "question": "Which City holds the record amount of NBA Championship titles?",
          "answer": "Boston"
        },
        {
          "points": 300,
          "question": "He holds the record for scoring the most points in a single game",
          "answer": "Wilt Chamberlain"
        },
        {
          "points": 400,
          "question": "The only current Canadian NBA Team plays in what city",
          "answer": "Toronto"
        },
        {
            "points": 500,
            "question": "Whose silhouette serves as the modern day logo of the NBA?",
            "answer": "Jerry West"
          }
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Athlete Jersey #",
      "questions": [
        {
          "points": 100,
          "question": "Tom Brady - NFL",
          "answer": "12"
        },
        {
          "points": 200,
          "question": "Barry Sanders - NFL",
          "answer": "20"
        },
        {
          "points": 300,
          "question": "Mike Piazza - MLB",
          "answer": "31"
        },
        {
          "points": 400,
          "question": "Emmitt Smith",
          "answer": "22"
        },
        {
            "points": 500,
            "question": "Mickey Mantle",
            "answer": "7"
          }
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "MLB History",
      "questions": [
        {
          "points": 100,
          "question": "Who was the first MLB Player to have his number retired?",
          "answer": "Lou Gherig"
        },
        {
          "points": 200,
          "question": "Whose baseball card is valued at the highest of all time",
          "answer": "Honus Wagner"
        },
        {
          "points": 300,
          "question": "How many No Hitters did Nolan Ryan Have",
          "answer": "7"
        },
        {
          "points": 400,
          "question": "Which player has appeared in the most world series games",
          "answer": "Yogi Berra"
        },
        {
            "points": 500,
            "question": "In what year was the first World Series Held",
            "answer": "1903"
          }
      ]
    },
    {
        "category": "NFL Nicknames",
        "questions": [
          {
            "points": 100,
            "question": "Broadway Joe",
            "answer": "Joe Namath"
          },
          {
            "points": 200,
            "question": "Matty Ice",
            "answer": "Matt Ryan"
          },
          {
            "points": 300,
            "question": "Fitzmagic",
            "answer": "Ryan Fitzpatrick"
          },
          {
            "points": 400,
            "question": "Iron Mike",
            "answer": "Mike Ditka"
          },
          {
              "points": 500,
              "question": "Muscle Hamster",
              "answer": "Doug Martin"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "NFL Randoms",
        "questions": [
          {
            "points": 100,
            "question": "How Many Players are legally on the field for each team during each play",
            "answer": "11"
          },
          {
            "points": 200,
            "question": "How Many NFL Teams hae 5 or more Super Bowl Victories?",
            "answer": "4"
          },
          {
            "points": 300,
            "question": "What Round Was Tom Brady Drafted In",
            "answer": "6"
          },
          {
            "points": 400,
            "question": "Who Caught the Ball in the famous play known as THE CATCH>",
            "answer": "Dwight Clark"
          },
          {
              "points": 500,
              "question": "How Many NFL Teams use Birds as their Mascots?",
              "answer": "5"
            }
        ]
    },
  ];

  